[
    {
        "question": "The phrase \"attachment to\" in line 1 is closest in meaning to ..........",
        "options": [
            "control of",
            "distance from",
            "curiosity about",
            "preference for"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "The word \"protruding\" in line 12 is closest in meaning to ................",
        "options": ["parallel", "simple", "projecting", "important"],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The relationship of a mortise and a tenon is most similar to that of ...............",
        "options": [
            "a lock and a key",
            "a book and its cover",
            "cup and a saucer",
            "a hammer and a nail"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "For what purpose did woodworkers use an auger ..................",
        "options": [
            "To whittle a peg",
            "To make a tenon",
            "To drill a hole",
            "To measure a panel"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following were NOT used in the construction of colonial furniture?",
        "options": ["Mortises", "Nails", "Hinges", "Screws"],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The author implies that colonial metalworkers were................",
        "options": [
            "unable to make elaborate parts",
            "more skilled than woodworkers",
            "more conservative than other colonists",
            "frequently employed byjoiners"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The word \"shield\" in line 20 is closest in meaning to ................",
        "options": ["decorate", "copy", "shape", "protect"],
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "The word \"they\" in line 25 refers to ................",
        "options": ["designs", "types", "colonists", "all"],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The author implies that the colonial joiners ..................",
        "options": [
            "were highly paid",
            "based their furniture on English models",
            "used many specialized tools",
            "had to adjustto using new kinds of wood in New England"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following terms does the author explain in the passage?",
        "options": [
            "\"millennia\"",
            "\"joiners\"",
            "\"whittled\"",
            "\"blacksmiths\""
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    }
]
